grandcentral.com 2003-12-02

# Grand Central Communications

|   
Privacy Policy  

Respecting the privacy and confidentiality of your personal information is important to Grand Central Communications. During your use of the public web site ([www.grandcentral.com](http://www.grandcentral.com/)), you may be asked to voluntarily provide certain personally identifiable information, such as your name, job title, company name, phone number, email address or postal address. We collect this information in order to enhance your use of the web site or for purposes such as facilitating correspondence with you or registering your entitlement to access certain special features of the web site. Grand Central will share this information with third parties who are directly related to Grand Central's business or who are specific to supporting its customers or partners only if this is indicated in your profile. If you would like to be removed from our mailing list or database, please send an email at any time to [unsubscribe@grandcentral.com](mailto:unsubscribe@grandcentral.com).

Information about all web site users  
If you browse the public portions of the Web Site, you do so anonymously. Grand Central does not collect your personally identifiable information unless you voluntarily provide it to us. Grand Central may automatically collect certain non-personally identifiable information regarding your use of the web site, such as the Internet Protocol address of your computer, your Internet Service Provider, the type of computer and operating system you are using, the pages read and any content downloaded. This information is not linked to you as an individual user. Rather, it is recorded as general statistical information, which may be used and disclosed to others by Grand Central to monitor use of the web site, to help diagnose technical problems, to improve the web site and generally to enable us to provide you with the best possible web experience. That information may be retained for future statistical analysis and other purposes.

Voluntary Provision of Personal Information  
We require customers who register to use the services ("Services") offered on our web site to give us certain contact information, such as their name, company name, address, phone number, and e-mail address.

Grand Central uses the information that we collect to set up services for individuals and their organizations. We may also use the information to contact customers to further discuss customer interest in our company, the services that we provide, and to send information regarding our company or partners, such as promotions and events. Customers may be invited to receive an email newsletter by providing an email address. Customer email addresses will not be distributed or shared. Customers can opt out of being contacted by us, or receiving such information from us, at any time by sending an email to [support@grandcentral.com](mailto:support@grandcentral.com). Separately, customers are also asked to provide an email address when registering for the Service, in order to receive a username and password. We may also email information regarding updates to the service or company. Again, email will not be distributed or shared and customers can opt out of receiving any communication by emailing support@grandcentral.com at the time it is distributed, or at the time any user registers for the service.

Except as we explicitly state at the time we request information, or as provided for in the Grand Central Terms of Use, we do not disclose to any third party the information provided.

Securing Your Information  
To help protect the confidentiality of your personally identifiable information, Grand Central employs security safeguards appropriate to the sensitivity of the information. Nevertheless, all security and privacy risks cannot be eliminated.

Additionally, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be perfectly secure. As a result, while we try to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure or guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk.

Other Web Sites  
The Grand Central web site may contain links to other web sites. When you click on one of those links, you will connect with another web site. Grand Central has no responsibility for, or control over, any linked web sites or their privacy policies or the manner in which they collect, use or disclose your personally identifiable information.

Terms of Use Agreement  
The Terms of Use Agreement for the service contains important provisions, including provisions disclaiming, limiting or excluding Grand Central's liability for your use of the service and the software development kit(s), and provisions relating to the law and jurisdiction for the resolution of any disputes regarding those matters. Each of those provisions apply to any issues that may arise in relation to this Privacy Policy, and are of the same force and effect as if they had been reproduced directly in this Privacy Policy.

Privacy Policy Changes  
This Privacy Policy may be changed from time to time. Revised Privacy Policies will be posted here.

Your Consent  
By using the Web Site and/or the Grand Central Service, you consent to the collection and use of any information in the manner we describe.

Your Comments  
If you have any comments or questions about this Privacy Policy or your personal information, please contact us at [support@grandcentral.com](mailto:support@grandcentral.com).

|  |  |
